ocala4sale.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy - USA4SALE Blog

At USA4SALE.NET, LLC (“USA4SALE”), we take your privacy very seriously. This policy states what happens to your personal information when you use our Web sites. This policy does not apply to the companies and websites that we advertise or endorse. Please visit their Web sites for their policy regarding how they handle personal information.

By using, browsing and/or accessing the site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  Your visit to the site and any dispute over privacy is subject to the [Terms of Service](http://blog.usa4sale.net/terms-of-service/), including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of Florida.  Use of this site is strictly voluntary.  **If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use for the site, you must immediately log off the site and may not use the site.**

**What We Collect**  
When you use our sites we may collect several pieces of information from you including your name, email address, phone number, your ad, your feedback, discussions and posts to our message boards, and where applicable physical or billing address, and billing information.  Additionally, our servers collect information when you view our site or post an ad or response, including browser and computing device information, referrer information, timestamp, page URL, and your IP address. Our servers collect this information so that we may analyze trends, administer the site, improve site performance, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

You will see that the amount and type of information required by us depends on the activity you are engaging in on the site.  For free ads, we require a valid phone number and email address. Paid ads require all information necessary for billing purposes including credit card, bank, and check information.

**What Happens to Information We Collect**  
Primarily you can expect that your ad, comments, feedback, and phone number will be published for all the World Wide Web to see. Most email addresses are hidden from public view. However, any web user may respond to your ad. Depending on how you reply, replying may disclose your email address and other contact information to those who respond to your ad. We publish not only to the Web, but also to a list of email subscribers, partner websites, and print publications. Your ad may appear in these places, as well.

We may retain all correspondence whether made by fax, email, or an online form. We may aggregate, categorize, and analyze the information received. Further, we may use the ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in your correspondence to develop, manufacture, and market products or services.

On occasion we may aggregate data collected on our site to analyze overall site usage.  Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information.  We may share this aggregate information with vendors, business partners, or other third parties.  We may also use this aggregate information for, among other things: quality control; conducting and publishing research and studies; development and testing products and services; identifying and monitoring trends; evaluating and monitoring equipment and technology used to provide products or services; marketing; and to help us plan for technical infrastructure requirements.

Although we make a good faith effort to keep all information secure, we cannot guarantee complete security or integrity of the information you transmit to or from this site, by e-mail or otherwise, and you provide such information at your own risk.  We cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration or destruction of data or personal information.  You acknowledge that: (1) there are security and privacy limitations in computer systems and on the Internet which are beyond our control; (2) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the site cannot be guaranteed; and (3) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with by a third party while such information or data is being used, transmitted, processed, or stored. All information may be stored indefinitely.

We may use the information you provide to us for particular activities, including, without limitation, processing an order; customer service and support; collections; employment; marketing and research; providing product, promotional and other information to you; and to contact you regarding administrative notices.  We must release your credit card information to credit card authorization service providers and our credit card-acquiring (merchant) bank to process your payment for ads purchased on this site and to facilitate refunds. We may share your e-mail address with our partner websites, affiliates, suppliers, and other third parties.

Many search engines and other sites archive or otherwise make available the content published on our site. Presently, we allow it so that people might find your ad more readily.

**What We Don’t Do**  
Although we publish a website of ads that make people’s phone numbers publicly available, we do not make or sell a simplified list of such information.

We do not knowingly collect information from a person under the age of 13. If we discover an ad was submitted by someone under 13, we will remove the ad from publication.

We do not make available for download, nor cause to download to the computers of users of our sites, programs that cause unsolicited advertising such as ad-ware, spy-ware, or browser hijacks.

**What We Recommend**  
We recommend a few ideas for safer buying and selling.

1\. Create and use an email address that is not your primary address. Many sites offer free email — Outlook, Yahoo!, Gmail, etc.  
3\. Place in your ad only the things that you want to be public.  
2\. Do not use an unlisted phone number.  
4\. Do not reply to messages offering more than the asking price. For more details, read [Safe Online Selling](http://blog.usa4sale.net/safe-online-selling/).

**Cookies, Tags, Web Beacons**  
USA4SALE may also use cookies, tags, and web beacons to collect information. Cookies, tags, and web beacons allow us to compile statistics and other information about how you use our sites. USA4SALE may collect information through these and similar tools about your web browsing activities such as the address of the page you are visiting, the address of the referrer page you previously visited, the time you are viewing the page, your browsing environment, your computing device, and your display settings.  We may use this data to analyze trends and improve the usability of our sites and products and services, to administer our sites, and to gather broad demographic statistics. We may also share such non-personally identifiable information with third parties on an aggregate basis.

In addition, we may use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet.  They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web sites, and your interaction with our products and services.  They may use cookies, tags, web beacons, and similar tools to serve ads and personalize your Web experience based on your prior visits to our Web site.  They may also use information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites to target advertisements for products and services.  This anonymous information is collected through the use of a cookie.  No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.  These third-party service providers do not know your name, phone number, address, e-mail address, or any other personally identifying information about you.  If you would like more information about this practice and to opt out of having this anonymous information used by our third party service providers, visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s consumer opt-out page by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Remarketing**

USA4SALE uses analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user’s previous visits to our websites.  We do not correlate personally identifiable information with remarketing lists, cookies or other anonymous identifiers. Visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google advertising opt-out page") or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Google Analytics opt-out page"). For more information, Google has provided these resources about their  [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746 "Google's Remarketing Privacy Guidelines"), [Policies](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=143465 "Google's Remarketing Policies"), and [Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363 "Google's Remarketing Privacy Restrictions").  
**  
**Law Enforcement and Third Parties****  
USA4SALE may disclose information in any of the following circumstances: (1) in response to a subpoena, search warrant, court order, or other legal process or request, or as may otherwise be required by applicable law or regulation; (2) to protect and defend USA4SALE’s rights or property or those of its affiliates, dealers, business partners, or others; or (3) as USA4SALE, in its sole discretion, believes is appropriate under exigent circumstances in response to a perceived threat to the personal safety, property, or rights of any other person or organization.

In order to protect our site and its users against potential fraud, we may verify with third parties the information you provide.

Since our database is a business asset, in the event we are reorganized or are sold to or merged with another company, you consent to the sale, assignment, or transfer of your personal information to a purchaser of all or substantially all of our business assets, or to an affiliate, as applicable.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may update this policy. Any use of the site following the date on which we implement changes to this Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of all such changes. Please stay informed of our current privacy policy by returning here.
